jildorshoes.com 2013-05-24

# Privacy Policy - Jildor Shoes Since 1949

  | 

JildorShoes.com Privacy Policy  
Last Updated April 26, 2010

Jildor Shoes ("Jildor") understands and respects your concerns about privacy. This notice describes Jildor's privacy policy as it pertains to the website at www.jildorshoes.com (the "Website"). We may from time-to-time revise this privacy policy, and the date of last revision will be available at the top of this page, so please be sure to check back periodically. By visiting the Website, you are acknowledging and accepting this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after changes have been posted to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

What information we collect: Jildor may ask for and collect from you personally identifiable and financial information at certain points throughout the Website. Depending on the information and/or services you request, you may be asked to provide your name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card or other financial account information, and other information. Once you provide your personal information, you are not anonymous to Jildor.

In addition to the information you knowingly provide, Jildor collects the domain names and IP addresses of its visitors, along with usage statistics (e.g., types of web browsers and operating systems used) and browsing history. This data is used to more efficiently operate Jildor's business, promote our products and services and administer the Website. Jildor may combine this information with the personally identifiable information it collects.

How Jildor uses your information: Jildor may use your information:

• To verify credit and process payments.

• To provide you with personalized content.

• To process and respond to inquiries.

• For the purposes for which you provided the information.

• To improve the content and navigability of the Website.

• To alert you to new Website features, special events, products and services.

• To enforce the Terms of Use.

In the future, we may sell some or all or our assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event of a sale of our assets including our database, customer information will be transferred. We will require buyers to honor our privacy policy.

Information Sharing with Third Parties: Jildor may disclose your personally identifiable information to another entity (i) for purposes of outsourcing one or more of the functions described in the previous section, including payment processing; (ii) to confirm or update information provided by you; (iii) to inform you of important information; and/or (iv) as a part of a sale of assets as described in the previous section. We may also share your information in response to a subpoena, legal order or official request, when we believe you have acted in violation of the Terms of Use, or when we believe that doing so may protect your safety or the safety of others.

Sharing and use of de-identified information: Information that is de-identified (stripped of any information that could be used to identify you) may be used by Jildor for any reason and shared freely with affiliates, partners and other third parties. This information is usually aggregated (combined with information from many other users), and may include information such as traffic patterns, trends in connection with various types of transactions, and other information.

How we collect information: In addition to the methods described above, we may also collect information using cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These methods permit us to collect various types of information, including which pages you visit, which of our email messages you read, and other information.

How we protect information: Jildor attempts to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal and financial information. Our servers are protected by reasonable physical and electronic security measures.

How you can view or update your personal or financial information: To ensure that you have as much control over your personally identifiable and financial information as possible, you may  
update your information by utilizing the Website or emailing us at:  
  
We will use reasonable efforts to process any change you make; provided, however, that requests to delete information are subject to Jildor's internal reporting and retention policies and all applicable legal obligations.

Children: This Website is not directed toward children under 13 years of age nor does Jildor knowingly collect information from children under 13. If you are under 13, please do not use this Website.

Links: The Website may contain links to third-party websites. Jildor is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

Your California Privacy Rights: Jildor does not disclose your information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.

Contacts: If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at:  

|
